http://www.uniquetruck.com/topic/privacy/

Response during COVID-19
Help
|
Browse Catalog
Questions?
Chat Now
or
Call (616) 531-8868
Login
View Cart (0)
Checkout
Cart (0)
ALL MANUFACTURERS
Cart (0)
Flat Rate Shipping Starts at $9.95
*Within the Contiguous USA. Click here for complete Shipping Policy
Same Day Shipping Available!
Second Day and Next Day options at Checkout on most items.
Flat Rate Shipping Starts at $9.95
Same Day Shipping Available!
Keeping your information private is important us. So we'll treat it with utmost care and protect the information you share with us. We won’t sell your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, credit card number or any other information.
We use state-of-the-art security measures to protect your information from unauthorized users.
NOTICE
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you create a Registration ID on the site, request a catalog, place an order or sign up for our email newsletters. We use your Personal Information for three primary purposes:
To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.
To help us create content most relevant to you.
To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from Unique Truck Equipment
SECURITY
Unique Truck Equipment has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.
We guarantee your e-commerce transactions to be 100% safe and secure. When you place orders or access your personal account information, you're utilizing a secure server software SSL, which encrypts your personal information before it's sent over the Internet. SSL is one of the safest encryption technologies available.
You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your user name and password, so do not share these with others.
COOKIES
Unique Truck Equipment uses "cookies" as part of our website. Our cookies tag each visitor's browser. These cookies do not disclose any personal information about the person using the browser. The cookies are used to study traffic and improve our website.
Cookies are used by third party vendors, including Google, to display ads based on a user's previous visits to Unique Truck Equipment's website. You can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Ads Preferences Manager. You can also opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION YOU SHARE
When you share your information with us, you provide us with your contact information, including your name and email address.
When you order from us, we ask for your credit card number and billing address. We use this information only to bill you for the product(s) you order at that time.
We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf (i.e. packaging, mailing, shipping, customer reviews). We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
Questions about this policy can be directed to our company compliance officer at (616) 531-8868.
Copyright 1996-2020 Unique Truck Equipment, Inc.
All Rights Reserved
Report A Site Issue
Shopping Cart:
0
Items
Your shopping cart is currently empty.
Discounts:
Total:
$0.00
Close
Checkout
Loading...
